Every moment counts.
My Life is a drama, romance film directed by Bruce Joel Rubin.
It seems that Bob Jones has everything a man could want, namely a
fulfilling job and a beautiful, pregnant wife, Gail.
But Bob's life is turned upside-down when he is diagnosed with cancer and given four
months to live -- not even enough time to see his first child's birth.
To cleanse himself of demons in his remaining days, Bob makes a video
diary, hoping to pass along some wisdom to his future child.
Along the way, he discovers a lot about himself.
Bob Jones, played by Michael Keaton.
Gail Jones, played by Nicole Kidman.
Paul Ivanovich, played by Bradley Whitford.
Bill Ivanovich, played by Michael Constantine.
Rose Ivanovich, played by Rebecca Schull.
Mr. Ho, played by Haing S. Ngor.
My Life is a 1993 American drama film written, directed and co-produced by
Bruce Joel Rubin, starring Michael Keaton and Nicole Kidman.
With a PG-13 rating, this film's worldwide box office gross was $54 million.
The film explores themes of baby, cancer, death,
expectant mother, reconciliation.
The tone is emotional.